Guide to the H. Elliott McClure Papers, 1947-1989.
McClure, H. Elliott papers
- Series I: Species Files and Banding Lists
  - Campephagidae
    - Scarlet Minivet (Pericrocotus flammeus) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Fiery Minivet (Pericrocotus igneus) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Bar-winged Flycatcher-shrike (Hemipus picatus) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Black-winged Cuckoo-shrike (Hemipus hirundinaceus) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Pied Cuckoo-shrike (Lalage nigra) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Lesser Greybird (Coracina fimbriata) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Wood-shrike (Tephrodornis pondiceriana) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - White-vented Cuckoo-shrike (Coracina novaehollandiae) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Mountain Minivet (Pericrocotus solaris) (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Barred Cuckoo-shrike (Coracina striata) (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Ashy Minivet (Pericrocotus divaricatus) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Dicruridae
    - Lesser Racquet-tailed Drongo (Dicrurus remifer) (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Large Racquet-tailed Drongo (Dicrurus paradiseus) (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Crow-billed Drongo (Dicrurus annectans) (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Bronzed Drongo (Dicrurus aeneus) (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Sciuridae
    - Horse-tail Squirrel (Sundasciurus hippurus) (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Prevost's Squirrel(Callosciurus prevosti) (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Cream-colored giant Squirrel (Ratufa affinis), Black Giant Squirrel (Ratufa bicolor) (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Plantain Squirrel (Callosciurus notatus) (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Grey-bellied Squirrel (Callosciurus caniceps) (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Slender Squirrel (Callosciurus Tenuis) (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Black-banded Squirrel (Callosciurus nigrovittatus) (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Pteropodidae
    - Spotted-winged Fruit Bat (Balionycteris maculata) (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Black-capped Fruit Bat (Chinorax melanocephala) (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Greater Musky Fruit Bat (Ptenochirus jagori) (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Horsefield's Fruit Bat (Cynopterus horsfieldi) (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Long-tongued Nectar Bat (Maegroglossus minimus) (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Fruit Bat (Maegroglossus lagochilus) (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Tailess fruit bat (Megaerops ecaudata) (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Dusky Fruit Bat (Penthetor lucasi) (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Lesser Short-nosed Fruit Bat (Cynopteris brachyotis) (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Geoffroy's Rousette (Rousettus amplexicaudatus) (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Small Flying Fox (Pteropus hypomelanus) (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Cave Necter Bat(Eonycteris spelaea) (Box 17, Folder 31B)
  - Hipposideridae
    - Diadem Roundleaf Bat (Hipposideros diadema) (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Bats I (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Bats II (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lacertilia
    - Lizards, Crestless, Flying Gecko, Monitors (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Flying Lizard (Draco volans) (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Tree Pit-viper (Trimeresurus puniceus) (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Skink (Mabuya multifasciata) (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Cercopithecidae
    - Leaf Monkeys (Colobinae) - Dusky (Trachypithecus obscurus), Banded (Presbytis femoralis) (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Long-tailed Macaque (Macaca fascicularis) (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Pig-tailed Macaque (Macaca nemestrina) (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Tupaiidae
    - Slow Loris (Tupaia glis) (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Hylobatidae
    - Lar Gibbon(Hylobates lar), Pileated Gibbon (Hylobates pileatus) (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - White-headed Gibbon (Hylobates lar) (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Siamang (Symphalangus syndactylus) (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Murinae
    - Malaysian Wood Rat (Rattus jalorensis) (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Annandale's Rat (Rattus annandalei) (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Bowers' White-toothed Rat (Rattus bowersi) (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Muller's Giant Rat (Rattus mulleri) (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Rattus canus (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Whitehead's Spiny Rat (Rattus whiteheadi) (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - White-bellied Rat (Rattus fulvescens) (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Rice-field Rat (Rattus argentiventer) (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Bowers' White-toothed Rat (Rattus bowersi) (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Long-tailed Giant Rat (Rattus sabanus) (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Brown Spiny Rat (Rattus rajah) (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Tragulidae
    - Mouse Deer (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Psittacidae
    - Loriquet (Loriculus galgulus) (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Long Tailed Parakeet (Psittacula longicuada) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Little Malay Parrot (Psittinus cyanurus) (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Tytonidae
    - Barn Owl (Tyto alba) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bay Owl (Phodilus badius) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Podargidae
    - Blyths Frogmouth (Batrachostomus affinis) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Gould's Frogmouth (Batrochostomus stellatus) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Caprimulgidae
    - Giant Nightjar (Melomys cerviniceps) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Lesser Night Hawk (Chordeiles minor) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Great-eared Nightjar (Eurostopodus temmincki) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Long-tailed Nightjar (Caprimulgus macrurus) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Migratory Nightjar (Caprimulgus indicus) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Strigidae
    - Burrowing Owl (Speotyto cunicularia) (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Screech Owl (Otus osio) (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Great Horned Owl (Bubo virginianus) (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Brown Wood Owl (Strix leptogrammica) (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Reddish Scops Owl (Otus rufescens) (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Brown Hawkowl (Minox scutulata) (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Long-eared Owl (Asio otus) (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Short-eared Owl (Asio flammeus) (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Eagle Owl (Bubo sumatranus) (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Ural Owl (Strix uralensis) (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Pygmy Owlet (Glaucidium brodies) (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Fish Owl (Keyupa ketupa) (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Lesser Scops Owl (Otus scops) (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Mountain Scops Owl (Otus spilocephalus) (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Collared Scops Owl (otus bakkamoena) (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Pycnonotidae
    - White-throated Bulbul (Criniger phaeocephalus) (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Scrub Bulbul (Criniger bres) (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Grey-bellied Bulbul (Pycnonotus cyaniventris) (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Large Olive Bulbul (Pycnonotus plumosus) (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Olive Bulbul (Pycnonotus plumosus) (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Yellow-vented Bulbul (Pycnonotus goiavier) (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Yellow Crowned Bulbul (Pycnonotus zeylonicus) (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Mountain Streaked Bulbul (Hypsipetes mcclellandii) (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Hairy-backed Bulbul (Hypsipetes criniger) (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Scaly-breasted Bulbul (Pycnonotus squamatus) (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Black and White Bulbul (Pycnonotus melanoleucos) (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Black-headed Bulbul (Pycnonotus atriceps) (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Crested Bulbul (Criniger ochraceus) (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Blanfird's Bulbul (Pycnonotus blanfordi) (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Brown-eared Bulbul (Criniger pallidus) (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Crested Brown Bulbul (Pycnonotus eutilotus) (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - White-eyed Brown Bulbul (Pycnonotus simplex) (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Red-eyed Brown Bulbul (Pycnonotus brunneus) (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Streaked Bulbul (Hypsipetes viridescens) (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Ashy Bulbul (Hypsipetes flavalus) (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Red-whiskered Bulbul (Pycnonotus jocosus) (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Olive-brown Bulbul (Pycnonotus robinsoni) (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Finsch's Bulbul (Criniger finschii) (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Lesser Olive-brown Bulbul (Pycnonotus erythropthalmus) (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Yellow-vented Bulbul (Pycnonotus goiaver) I (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Yellow-vented Bulbul (Pycnonotus goiaver) II (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Paridae
    - Black-capped Chickadee (Parus atricapillus) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Coal Tit (Parus ater) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Varied Tit (Parus varius) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Long-tailed Tit (Aegithalos caudatus) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Great Tit (Parus major) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Sultan Tit (Melanochlora sultanea) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Chestnut-backed Chickadee (Parus rufescens) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Mountain Chikadee (Parus gambeli) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Plain Titmouse (Baeolophus inornatus) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bush Tit (Psaltriparus minimus) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Certhidae
    - Brown Tree Creeper (Certhia familiaris) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Sittidae
    - White-breasted Nuthatch (Sitta carolinensis) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Deep Blue Nuthatch (Sitta azurea) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Nuthatch (Sitta europaea) (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Velvet-fronted Nuthatch (Sitta frontalis) (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Red-breasted Nuthatch (Sitta canadensis) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Timaliidae
    - Striped Babbler (Pellorneum ruficeps) (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Scaly-breasted Wren (Pnoepyga puilla) (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - White-necked Tree Babbler (Stachyris leucotis) (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Lesser Red-headed Tree Babbler (Malacopteron cinereum) (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Black-capped Babbler (Pellorneum capistratum) (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Plain Babbler (Malacopteron affine) (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Greater Red-headed Tree Babbler (Malacopteron Magnum) (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Wrentit (Chamaea fasciata) (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Grey-headed Tree Babbler (Stachyris poliocephala) (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Silver-eared Mesia (Leothrix argentauris) (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Mountain Nun Babbler (Acippe morrisonia) (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Black-crowned Shrike Babbler (Pteruthius erythopterus) (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Mountain Brown Babbler (Pellorneum tickelli) (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - White-bellied Crested Babbler (Yuhina zantholeuca) (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - White-throated Jungle Babbler (Malacopteron albogulare) (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Brown-headed Tree Babbler (Malacopteron magnirostre) (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Black-eared Shrike Babbler (Pteruthius melanotus) (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Streaked Wren Babbler (Napothera brevicaudata) (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Blue-winged Siva (Minla cyanouroptera) (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Himalayan Cutia (Cutia nipalensis) (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Pygymy Wren Babbler (Pnoepyga pusilla) (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Wrays Scimitar Babbler (Pomatorhinus hypoleucos) (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Golden-headed babbler (Stachyris chrysaea) (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Chestnut-headed Nun Thrush (Alcippe castaneiceps) (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Chestnut-capped Laughing Thrush (Garrulax mitratus) (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Yellow-breasted Tit Babbler (Macronus gularis) (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Chestnut-tailed Siva (Minla strigula) (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Long-tailed Sibia (Heterophasia picaoides) (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Scimitar Babbler (Pomatorhinus schisticeps) (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Fluffy-backed Babbler (Macronus ptilosus) (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Black-necked Tree Babbler (Stachyrus nigricollis) (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Common Nun Babbler (Alcippe poiocephala) (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - White-bellied Crested Babbler (Yuhina zantholeuca) (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Red-rumped Babbler (Stachyris maculata) (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Red-winged Tree Babbler (Stachyris erythroptera) (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Short-tailed Babbler (trichastoma malaccensis) (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Ferruginous Babbler (Trichastoma bicolor) (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Common Brown Babbler (Trichastoma abbotti) (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Grey-throated Babbler (Stachyris nigriceps) (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Red-headed Laughing Thrush (Garrulax erythrocephalus) (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Mangrove Brown Babbler (Trichastoma rostrata) (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Upupidae
    - Hoopoe (Upupa epops) (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Coraciidae
    - Broad-billed Roller (Eurystomus orientalis) (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Burmese Roller (Coracias benghalensis) (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Meropidae
    - Brown-breasted Bee Eater (Merops superciliosus) (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Blue-throated Bee Eater (Merops viridis) (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Red-bearded Bee Eater (Nyctiornis amictus) (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Bay-headed Bee Eater (Merops leschenaulti) (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Hemiprocnidae
    - White-whiskered Tree Swift (Hemiprocne comata) (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - Crested Tree Swift (Hemiprocne longinpennis) (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - Truchulidae
    - Calliope Hummingbird (Stellula calliope) (Box 21, Folder 72)
    - Rufus Hummingbird (Selasphorus rufus) (Box 21, Folder 73)
    - Allen Hummingbird (Selasphorus alleni) (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Anna Hummingbird (Calypte anna) (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - Black-chinned Hummingbird (Archilochus alexandri) (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Trogonidae
    - Cinnamon-rumped Trogon (Harpactes orrhophaeus) (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Red-naped Trogon (Harpactes Kosumba) (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Diard's Trogon (Harpactes diardii) (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Red-rumped Trogon (Harpactes duvauceli) (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Red-head Trogon (Harpactes erythrocephalus) (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - Thraupidae
    - Western Tanager (Piranga ludoviciana) (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - Estrildidae
    - Chestnut Munia (Lonchura malacca) (Box 21, Folder 84)
    - Spotted Munia (Lonchura punctulata) (Box 21, Folder 85)
    - White-headed Munia (Lonchura maja) (Box 21, Folder 86)
    - Long-tailed Munia (Erythura prasina) (Box 21, Folder 87)
    - White-bellied Munia (Lonchura leucogastra (Box 21, Folder 88)
    - Black-headed Munia (Lonchura atricapilla) (Box 21, Folder 89)
    - Sharp-tailed Munia (Lonchura striata) (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - Passeridae
    - Pegu House Sparrow (Passer flaveolus) (Box 21, Folder 91)
    - Tree Sparrow (Passer Montanus) (Box 21, Folder 92)
    - Russet Sparrow (Passer rutilans) (Box 21, Folder 93)
  - Ploecidae
    - Baya Weaver (Ploceus philippinus) (Box 21, Folder 94)
    - Manyar Weaver (Ploceus manyar) (Box 21, Folder 95)
  - Corvidae
    - Rook (Corvus frugilegus) (Box 21, Folder 98)
    - Common Crow (Corvus brachyrhynchos) (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Scrub Jay (Aphelocoma californica) (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Raven (Corvus corax) (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Steller's Jay (Cyanocitta stelleri) (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Slender-billed Crow (Corvus enca) (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - White-winged Jay (Platysmurus leucopterus) (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - House Crow (Corvus splendens) (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Crested Jay (Platylophus galericulatus) (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Blue Magpie (Cyanopica cyanus) (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Carrion Crow (Corvus corone) (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Magpie (Pica pica) (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Jungle Crow (Corvus levaillantii) (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Nutcracker (Nucifraga caryocatactes) (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Blue-green Magpie (Kitta chinensis) (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Racquet-tailed Magpie (Crypsirina temia) (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Bucerotidae
    - Hornbills (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Southern Pied Hornbill (Anthracocerus coronatus) (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wreathed Hornbill (Rhyticeros undulatus) (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Helmeted Hornbill (Rhinoplax vigil) (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Rhinocerus Hornbill (Buceros rhinoceros) (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Long-crested Hornbill (Berenicornis comatus) (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bushy-crested Hornbill (Anorrhinus galeritus) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Black Hornbill (Anthrecoceros malayanus) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Capitonidae
    - Grey Headed Barbet (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Muller's Barbet (Cyanops oorti) (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Lineated Dull Barbet (Megalaima zeylandicus) (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Many-colored Barbet (Megalaima rafflesi) (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Fire-tufted Barbet (Psilopogon pyrolophus) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Cinclidae
    - American Dipper (Cinclus mexicanus) (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Pallas Dipper (Cinclus pallasii) (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Troglodytidae
    - Rock Wren (Salpinctes obsoletus) (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Long-billed Marsh Wren (Telmatodytes palustris) (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Bewick's Wren (Thryomanes bewickii) (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - House Wren (Troglodytes aedon) (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Wren (Troglodytes troglodytes) (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mimidae
    - Mockingbird (Mimus polyglottos) (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Californian Thrasher (Toxostoma redivivum) (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Turdidae
    - Grey-headed Thrush (Turdus obscurus) (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Straits Robin (Copsychus saularis) (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Chestnut-naped Forktail (Enicurus ruficapillus) (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Japanese Robin (Erithacus akahige) (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Rufous-headed Robin (Erithacus ruficeps) (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Varied Thrush (Ixoreus naevius) (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Hermit Thrush (Hylocichla guttata) (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Swainson's Thrush (Hylocichla ustalata) (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - White-tailed Blue Robin (Muscisylivia leucura) (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Townsend's Solitaire (Myadestes townsendi) (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Malayan Whistling Thrush (Myophoneus robinsoni) (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Daurian Redstart (Phoenicurus auroreus) (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Pied Siberian Stonechat (Saxicola caprata) (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Mountain Bluebird (Sialia currucoides) (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Blue Whistling Thrush (Myophonus coeruleus) (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Western Bluebird (Sialia mexicana) (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Siberian Bluetail (Erithacus cyanurus) (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Grey Thrush (Turdus cardis) (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Brown Thrush (Turdus chrysolaus) (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Dusky Thrush (Turdud naumanni) (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Shortwing (Brachypteryx leucophrys) (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Orange-tailed shama (Copsychus pyrropygus) (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Robin (Turdus migratorius) (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Pale Thrush (Turdus pallidus) (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Orange-headed Thrush (Zoothera citrina) (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - White's Ground Thrush (Zoothera dauma) (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Plain-backed Ground Thrush (Zoothera dixoni) (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Siberian Ground Thrush (Zoothera sibirica) (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Regulidae
    - Goldcrest (Regulus regulus) (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Alcedinidae
    - Belted Kingfisher (Megaceryle alcyon) (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Lesser Pied Kingfisher (Ceryle rudis) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Brown-winged Stork-billed Kingfisher (Pelargopsis amauroptera) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Stork-billed Kingfisher (Pelargopsis capensis) (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Banded Kingfisher (Lacedo pulchella) (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Whie-collared Kingfisher (Halcyon chloris) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - White-breasted Kingfisher(Halcyon smyrnensis) (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Black-capped Kingfisher (Halcyon pileata) (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Chestnut-collared Kingfisher (Halcyon concreta) (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Red-backed Kingfisher(Ceyx rufidorsus) (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Black-backed Kingfisher (Ceyx erithacus) (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Deep-blue Kingfisher (Alcedo meninting) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Blue-banded Kingfisher(Alcedo euryzona) (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Pied Kingfisher (Ceryle lugubris) (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Common Kingfisher (Alcedo athis) (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Ruddy Kingfisher (Halcyon coromanda) (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Oriolidae
    - Black-naped oriole (Oriolus chinensis) (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Black-headed Oriole (Oriolus xanthonotus) (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Series II: Banding Lists, Counts and Observation Files
  - Summary Tallies of Birds in the Konto Plain, 1951-1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lists of Birds at Mt. Brinchang (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Subang Lists, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mae Ping River (Thailand) Lists, December 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Rantau Panjang Lists, 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wat Phai Lom (Thailand) Lists, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Lists Comparing Forests, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Olive Grove Scout Work, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Sukumvit Bat Studies, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Coordinates of Banding Stations, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Totals of All Species Tallied in Malaya (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Mt. Takao, Japan, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mt. Takao, Japan, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Four Year Summary of Bird populations in the Tokyo Area, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Reports on Shin Hama (Ardeids in Japan), 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Heron and Egret Summaries (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Specimens Sent to Twomey and Col. Hunter (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hippoboscid Studies of Banded Birds (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and Notes: Birds of Japan (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Summaries of Bird Populations in the Tokyo Area, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Summary of Tallies in Japan, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Composition of Bird Waves in Malaya (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Birds of Wat Phai Lom as Tallied or Caught, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Blood Smears from Spotted Doves, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Conejo Valley Audubon Christmas Bird Count, 1974-1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Bird Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Japan Ornithological Survey: Ozuchi, 1951, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Japan Ornithological Survey: Aomori, Hokkaido, 1951, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Japan Ornithological Survey: Haneda, Chiba, Mitsubishi, Ueno, Meiji, Saitama, 1951, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Japan Ornithological Survey: Kyushu, Nagoya, Osaka, 1951, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Japan Ornithological Survey: Toyoma, Lake Yamanaka, Okinawa; Banding Lists: Korea, Malaya, Thailand, Singapore, 1951, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Banding Lists: Hokkaido, Kyushu, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Reports on Japanese Birds (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Records of Birds at Lighthouses, Japan, 1923-1939 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Organized Banding Lists I (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Organized Banding Lists II (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Organized Banding Lists III (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Rodent Longevity Summaries (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Analysis of Mosquitoes at Rantau Panjang (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Banding/Observations Data: Includes Large Graphs of Counts(?) and Weather Data at Numerous Stations, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Banding/Observations Data (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Rodent Summaries/Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 10B)
  - Mt. Brinchang - Daily Tallies, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Mt. Brinchang, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Ulu Gombak, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Ulu Gombak, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Japan: Shinhama and Sagiyama Populations, 1951-1954 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Japan: Population Counts at Shin Hama, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Federal Hill, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Japan: Shin Hama, 1951-1956 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Japan: Nesting Records - Shin Hama, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Japan: Hama Park, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Japan: Konto Plain (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Japan: Salt Flats Area, 1951-1956 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Japan: Asaka Area, 1951-1956 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Japan: Tamagawa Valley, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Japan: Population Counts Sagiyama, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Japan: Meiji Shrine, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Japan: Sagiyama, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Japan: Sagiyama, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Japan: Zama Area I, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Japan: Zama Area II, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Japan: Miyakejima, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Japan: Kikkawa and Nagoya, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Japan: Yoshii and Wakkanai, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - japan: Yoshii Saitama Data, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Palau Jarak, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Birds of Tioman, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Bukit Besi, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Fort Betis, Ulu Kelontan, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Ulu Bernam, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)